nearly forgot to set up the video today
yesterday I forgot to meditate but I'm
had an epiphany when I did a marathon
meditation / turned into a nap and that
is that my what I've seen is my greatest
weakness is that I don't know enough
that I don't have the energy as my
greatest strength and that's probably
the truth for a lot of us that how that
what we have to overcome is what makes
us wonderful what we have what comes
easily just comes easily to us that
there isn't as much beauty there as what
it is hard or nearly impossible that's
easy for the rest of the world and that
I've had issues with my health for the
past over a decade means that I well
finding that solution I get to find that
solution for for everyone and that I
have issues with relationships I think I
talked about this yesterday in my video
actually and that I have issues in
relationships means I get to solve that
and it means more love and connection
for everyone and that's exciting and one
of my biggest things that I've talked
about before is this idea that I don't
know and where I don't know things is
where I'm gonna create solutions for
everybody and so I don't know use to my
greatest obstacle and now it's my
greatest driver for instance with health
I don't know I don't know what caused my
brain tumors I don't know why I'm the
one with them I don't know how to
prevent them in the future I don't know
exactly well now I know why I had them
but I don't know who I can trust my
specialists because I've been given
faulty information and faulty diagnose
disease time and time again and so the
things that I want to know I want
everyone to know
I want to be able to easily look up
online if from a trustworthy source
exactly what science says an acoustic
neuroma is and why it's there and who
gets them and what being single-sided
death means and what fibromyalgia means
what chronic fatigue means and I want to
be able to and that's like for everyone
in society right that's anyone two goats
an acoustic neuroma it's gonna be but
also my individual health I want to be
able to track my health my energy levels
what happens when I eat this food versus
this food because my brain after
undergoing radiation and I don't know if
it ever would have been able to do that
to be able to see all of those patterns
I'm not the best at it it's really hard
for me unless a completely instant the
second I put something to my mouth that
I get a stomach ache or that I get
mental fog it's hard for me to know what
foods lead to those problems and I want
to know and so the more I'm able to
facilitate or weed together because I'm
not making it myself the creation of
apps that share technology error
information it's already out there such
as scientific literature in an
understandable and usable format so
grading the science and putting in data
points so we can use them for other
things so that when those data points
change and shift based on new studies it
ripples down and changes all of the data
points that were based on it after and
you don't have to go in and do that
every time there's there's a new
discovery because they're based on the
previous ones and that were able to
create tracking information like a
Fitbit that is accessible to everybody
for most people and is it allows me to
track my mood my pain levels my food up
and eating way as easily as possible and
if I can just tell me what I was eating
that would be great I knew and you would
have to input it can just take a picture
knows about the ingredients wouldn't
that be awesome I don't think that's
today's technology but
I just feel a lot of days I feel low
because of my health that it's but it's
all it's been such a gift because having
this time I was out I wouldn't have had
this time off of work this time to
myself it was time to create if I'd been
healthy and if I'd been healthy I
wouldn't have as much sympathy for
people who share my disability or other
disabilities or other struggles and in
solving this very personal problem for
myself I'm gonna be able to help so many
people solve it and so thank you thank
you to the universe for giving me brain
tumors for giving me faulty information
from doctors when when it came for my
single-sided deafness and the pain and
fatigue in my body and that I do have
the power to make it go away slowly
deliberately as I walk along the path I
was put here on the planet to walk I
become healthier and it's amazing so
yeah today is day six of my videos and
how I want to change the world with my
global cooperative involves sharing
knowledge that is normally seen as it
needs to come from an expert it needs to
come from a doctor it has to be this
hierarchy that I don't have access to
and I want to tear down that hierarchy I
want to give everybody access to the
knowledge that the elite in our society
have and with that knowledge we can live
happier healthier lives and all benefit